Taboubi Rihem

rihem.taboubi@medtech.tn

+216 52647257

linkedin.com/in/taboubi-rihem-3a3782231

Summary

I am a senior software engineering student at the South Mediterranean University with a strong interestin developing new skills. With a minim work experience I builtlots of skills related to the software engineering field. I drove a leading experience with my academic projects.

Experience

Busines Development Intern

SMU Career & Alumni Center

Sep 2023 - Present (4 months)

In this position I developed organizational skills. I successfully enhanced my communication skill and managed the stress pressure.

Data Science Intern

CodeClause

Oct 2023 - Nov 2023 (2 months)

I was assigned to develop a project of credit Card Fraud Detection using Google Colab/Jupiter Notebook/PowerBI Language- Python, R using a spesific dataset.

Angular developer Intern

Pro-ivr

Aug 2023 - Present (5 months)

I was assigned to the Web development

department where I worked on a real project with a

wide development team. In this project, I used the

Angular framework to develop the application to

align with architecture proposed.

Education



SMU - South Mediterranean University (MSB- MedTech-LCI)

Engineer's Degree, Computer Software Engineering

Licenses & Certifications



Meta Principles of UX/UI Design - Meta

Skills

User Experience (UX) • User Interface Design • Microsoft Word • Microsoft Office • Web Development • Mobile Application Development • R (Programming Language)

Honors & Awards

Ambassador Appreciation Certificate - IEEE PES-HAC

Dec 2023